{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733444488","data":{"timestamp":" 947733444488"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_n-f-b"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733448823","data":{"timestamp":" 947733448823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_y-f-k"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733453944","data":{"timestamp":" 947733453944"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-j-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733459532","data":{"timestamp":" 947733459532"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-u-f"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733463994","data":{"timestamp":" 947733463994"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_p-n-f"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733468884","data":{"timestamp":" 947733468884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733472735","data":{"timestamp":" 947733472735"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-n-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733496371","data":{"timestamp":" 947733496370"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_p-s-f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733503494","data":{"timestamp":" 947733503494"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-s"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733507021","data":{"timestamp":" 947733507021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-z-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733510163","data":{"timestamp":" 947733510162"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-z-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733519116","data":{"timestamp":" 947733519115"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-z-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733530987","data":{"timestamp":" 947733530986"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-z-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733584685","data":{"timestamp":" 947733584685"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 90ad9f50-b231-49b9-a64f-4533fc44f53a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-z-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733596599","data":{"timestamp":" 947733596598"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_r-f-l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733603872","data":{"timestamp":" 947733603872"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_r-f-l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733608047","data":{"timestamp":" 947733608047"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-l"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733611763","data":{"timestamp":" 947733611763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_b-f-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733616380","data":{"timestamp":" 947733616379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-s-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733619380","data":{"timestamp":" 947733619379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-ch-g"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733623248","data":{"timestamp":" 947733623248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_w-ch-f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733626409","data":{"timestamp":" 947733626409"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-l-ch"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733629614","data":{"timestamp":" 947733629613"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_v-z-f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733634825","data":{"timestamp":" 947733634825"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_v-z-f"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733638141","data":{"timestamp":" 947733638141"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_s-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733643534","data":{"timestamp":" 947733643533"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_s-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733651567","data":{"timestamp":" 947733651567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_s-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733655104","data":{"timestamp":" 947733655103"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733660851","data":{"timestamp":" 947733660850"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" cfb9a366-efc5-4cf7-ab70-ecd1eaaf0aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733675139","data":{"timestamp":" 947733675139"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-l-ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733681721","data":{"timestamp":" 947733681721"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-l"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733695197","data":{"timestamp":" 947733695197"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-s-d"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733698130","data":{"timestamp":" 947733698130"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-ch-g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733701856","data":{"timestamp":" 947733701856"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_w-ch-f"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733705334","data":{"timestamp":" 947733705334"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_v-z-f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733708712","data":{"timestamp":" 947733708712"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_s-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733714638","data":{"timestamp":" 947733714638"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_r-f-l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733732365","data":{"timestamp":" 947733732365"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_r-f-l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733735512","data":{"timestamp":" 947733735512"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-w"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733738853","data":{"timestamp":" 947733738853"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_b-f-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733744623","data":{"timestamp":" 947733744622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_f_b-f-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734292913","data":{"timestamp":" 947734292910"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 561d4452-9372-4610-829c-a17784e93030"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.89"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_f_b-f-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734292989","data":{"timestamp":" 947734292989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ab3d0ab8-d6f8-4912-b642-c212e7155974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_69"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734301758","data":{"timestamp":" 947734301758"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ab3d0ab8-d6f8-4912-b642-c212e7155974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_69"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734308378","data":{"timestamp":" 947734308377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ab3d0ab8-d6f8-4912-b642-c212e7155974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_69"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734314648","data":{"timestamp":" 947734314648"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ab3d0ab8-d6f8-4912-b642-c212e7155974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_69"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734322323","data":{"timestamp":" 947734322323"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ab3d0ab8-d6f8-4912-b642-c212e7155974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_69"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734331379","data":{"timestamp":" 947734331378"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ab3d0ab8-d6f8-4912-b642-c212e7155974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_69"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734343125","data":{"timestamp":" 947734343125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734348662","data":{"timestamp":" 947734348661"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734354188","data":{"timestamp":" 947734354187"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734358530","data":{"timestamp":" 947734358530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734364621","data":{"timestamp":" 947734364621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734370356","data":{"timestamp":" 947734370356"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734375654","data":{"timestamp":" 947734375654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734382104","data":{"timestamp":" 947734382104"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734389887","data":{"timestamp":" 947734389887"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734395090","data":{"timestamp":" 947734395090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734400960","data":{"timestamp":" 947734400960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734406879","data":{"timestamp":" 947734406879"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734423097","data":{"timestamp":" 947734423097"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734429504","data":{"timestamp":" 947734429504"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734436872","data":{"timestamp":" 947734436871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734449082","data":{"timestamp":" 947734449081"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734452632","data":{"timestamp":" 947734452632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734455609","data":{"timestamp":" 947734455609"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734459203","data":{"timestamp":" 947734459203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734462394","data":{"timestamp":" 947734462394"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734465627","data":{"timestamp":" 947734465627"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734471598","data":{"timestamp":" 947734471598"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734475684","data":{"timestamp":" 947734475684"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734481026","data":{"timestamp":" 947734481026"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734484849","data":{"timestamp":" 947734484848"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734488612","data":{"timestamp":" 947734488612"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734491641","data":{"timestamp":" 947734491640"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734494987","data":{"timestamp":" 947734494987"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734499269","data":{"timestamp":" 947734499269"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734502861","data":{"timestamp":" 947734502860"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734508629","data":{"timestamp":" 947734508629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734548038","data":{"timestamp":" 947734548036"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" dce41419-65ea-44da-ad22-8453e3c306e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734557186","data":{"timestamp":" 947734557186"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734560860","data":{"timestamp":" 947734560860"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734564322","data":{"timestamp":" 947734564322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734568157","data":{"timestamp":" 947734568157"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734571654","data":{"timestamp":" 947734571653"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734575107","data":{"timestamp":" 947734575107"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734578748","data":{"timestamp":" 947734578748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734582253","data":{"timestamp":" 947734582253"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734588903","data":{"timestamp":" 947734588903"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734595679","data":{"timestamp":" 947734595679"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734598970","data":{"timestamp":" 947734598970"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734607085","data":{"timestamp":" 947734607085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734614350","data":{"timestamp":" 947734614350"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734622758","data":{"timestamp":" 947734622758"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734625948","data":{"timestamp":" 947734625947"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734630620","data":{"timestamp":" 947734630619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734634022","data":{"timestamp":" 947734634022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734637886","data":{"timestamp":" 947734637886"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734643070","data":{"timestamp":" 947734643070"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734647571","data":{"timestamp":" 947734647571"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734653856","data":{"timestamp":" 947734653856"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734657396","data":{"timestamp":" 947734657396"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734665051","data":{"timestamp":" 947734665051"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734668164","data":{"timestamp":" 947734668163"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734674039","data":{"timestamp":" 947734674038"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734677365","data":{"timestamp":" 947734677365"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734680306","data":{"timestamp":" 947734680306"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734686060","data":{"timestamp":" 947734686059"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734693257","data":{"timestamp":" 947734693256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 3d150d37-0f6b-4918-ab90-28ddedb7433d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734704509","data":{"timestamp":" 947734704508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734709459","data":{"timestamp":" 947734709459"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GUNIA"," userResponse":" GUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734711011","data":{"timestamp":" 947734711011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" GAUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734714402","data":{"timestamp":" 947734714402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gauni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734715952","data":{"timestamp":" 947734715952"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" GOLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734719533","data":{"timestamp":" 947734719533"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" goli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734721096","data":{"timestamp":" 947734721096"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" giza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734724463","data":{"timestamp":" 947734724463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" giza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734725713","data":{"timestamp":" 947734725712"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734726014","data":{"timestamp":" 947734726014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-G.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734750184","data":{"timestamp":" 947734750183"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734750290","data":{"timestamp":" 947734750290"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4c13128b-c2e9-4aae-9285-fa27ae8d0020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-G.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734760508","data":{"timestamp":" 947734760508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_12-14-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734769742","data":{"timestamp":" 947734769742"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_12-14-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734774911","data":{"timestamp":" 947734774911"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734780593","data":{"timestamp":" 947734780593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734784890","data":{"timestamp":" 947734784890"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_8-12-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734789822","data":{"timestamp":" 947734789822"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-13-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734794501","data":{"timestamp":" 947734794498"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-6-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734799309","data":{"timestamp":" 947734799309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-14-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734805632","data":{"timestamp":" 947734805632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-14-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734810002","data":{"timestamp":" 947734810002"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734814905","data":{"timestamp":" 947734814905"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734821668","data":{"timestamp":" 947734821668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734831348","data":{"timestamp":" 947734831348"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734832915","data":{"timestamp":" 947734832915"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" ac33f152-c073-4bb7-b3c7-d799bb66db5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734847070","data":{"timestamp":" 947734847070"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_b-m-g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734864065","data":{"timestamp":" 947734864065"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_w-g-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734868072","data":{"timestamp":" 947734868071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-m-h"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734873239","data":{"timestamp":" 947734873239"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_t-k-g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734877648","data":{"timestamp":" 947734877648"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_p-g-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734882789","data":{"timestamp":" 947734882789"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_t-r-g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734886251","data":{"timestamp":" 947734886251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_w-g-v"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734892049","data":{"timestamp":" 947734892048"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_w-g-v"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734895929","data":{"timestamp":" 947734895929"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_i-g-n"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734900336","data":{"timestamp":" 947734900336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_h-v-g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734905928","data":{"timestamp":" 947734905928"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_h-v-g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734910508","data":{"timestamp":" 947734910508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_l-z-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734916278","data":{"timestamp":" 947734916277"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 2643b863-e0f1-42e4-b732-732f30c0bdf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_g_l-z-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734928657","data":{"timestamp":" 947734928657"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4628ef2b-2cb0-403d-8865-7a3a969f0a54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-m-h"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734933814","data":{"timestamp":" 947734933813"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000113_061707"," gameId":" 4628ef2b-2cb0-403d-8865-7a3a969f0a54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.90"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-m-h"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}